hi everyone myself
today welcome you all for a very new
topic is about
what are all the stocks he's gonna
impact from the stock
budget how the weather the the news is
in the positive side whether it is a new
citizen or
negative side how that is going to
impact on the sector wise
in the sector wise which are all the
stocks may impact on the positive side
which are the stocks which may impact on
the negative side
i'll be explaining that in the video so
the stocks
on radar with respect to the budget
though
in the first sector is about banks
public sector banks central bank bank of
baroda pnb banks
their state is expecting the
privatization there may be a prior
privatization may come that may impact
positive on these stocks like central
bank
bank of borrowed and pnb so there is
also a
bad bank commencement is there
there may be it is expected from the
street that s bank and idbi banks
are in the least that the stocks on
radar on the
on the budget day so next sector is
cigarettes
so every times the budget comes there is
some worry on the stocks like itc
got free film and vst there may be a tax
ike on the cigarette
so that may impact negative on the
stocks
so next is about infrastructure
investment is expecting from
the market so so market is expecting the
infrastructure investment
so whenever the financial crisis in the
country
in the past the government was invested
in the
infrastructure investments to push the
economy so that it will gonna
keep the growth of the gdp in the future
so the stocks on radar is with respect
to infrastructure investment
is lnt lassen and tour pro irb in from
dilip build con ncc or show build con
so in the last one we attack is related
to
a bharat child it may be a water tech
company there may be a reforms may come
that is the expected the stocks on radar
so next sector is about housing loan
segment
so the tax structure on the deductions
may be
increased so that may impact positive on
the stocks like
lac hfl can finns and hdfc these are the
three stocks which on radar on the
housing segments
and other stocks also the top three
stocks are like this so in the
affordable housing segment
the talk sale tax holiday is expected
dlf on the stocks and radar first second
one gold rate properties third one is
prestigious these are the three stocks
which are highly in focus
in affordable housing segment so
recently in
three four months back in the
maharashtra there is a stamp duty
there was a stamp duty cut so that it
was impacted
positive on the stocks like this dlf
gorget properties
real prestige estates so that is may be
expected from the budget also
so next sector is the power supply
reforms
in is there any power for power supplier
reforms may expected
so that may impact positive on the
stocks like ntpc
power grid nhpc in the public sector
side
so in the private sector tata power
adani power
torrent power these are the stocks on
focus next is
iron ore exposed higher duty if there is
higher duty
in the exports that may impact on the
stocks like tata steel
jsw steel jsbl so next
coking call import duty the state is
expecting the no duty
that may impact positive on the stocks
like tata steel jsw and jspl
next sector is insurance is there any
more deduction on the medic line that
may impact positive on the stocks like
icc loan board
and new india assurance there is also an
expectation for
insurance sector that more fdi limit
so the present fbi limit is at 49
percentage
so the street is expecting to hike that
limit to
74 percentage so it may impact positive
on
the stocks like this so next is form of
pli scheme is there any form of pla
scheme exp
a reforms may come so that may impact
the positive on the stocks like db slab
granules india and iowa chemical
so next is comes to exports in parma
the stocks on radar
which is gonna impact positive on the
scheme which is gonna come
from the budget is new road tape skip
that may impact positive on the stocks
like greenform landmark pharma
sun farmer and doctors ready slab these
are the shocks on focus
and in the healthcare segment in the
covered situation we expected
and we have seen the air spinning in the
hospital side apollo hospital and 40s
on the radar next is come to hospital
building side max
that's on the focus so this is all about
the sector wise the stocks-wise
the specific what the market is
expecting from the budget
and what the budget may give and
it's going to impact on the stocks like
like this whatever expand
from the video so this is the stocks on
trader
so i think this video is useful for the
people those who want to watch the
stocks
on the budget day and after budget day
how it's going to impact on this kind of
stocks
whether it is in the positive side
whether it is the negative side
wait when it comes from when the
outcome of the project so this is all
about the
today's video in the next video i'll be
coming up with the very new topic
called budget estimation for fi 22
the profit and loss account of the
government so till then bye bye
thank you all do like subscribe to my
channel channel
for further videos about the budget